[{"answer": "I'm just trying to live this interesting life we all have in front of us.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "You're a kind of fiery, emotional, soulful character, aren't you -- on and often stage?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "I think at this point, I'm 51 now, I've realized, oh, it's just a journey.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "When you look at your extraordinary life professional and personal, how do you feel now about where you've arrived, where you are right now?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "You're never actually going to arrive, are you?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Ooh.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What's been the moment if I could replay it for you, you'd relive?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "That was 1994 unplugged, MTV.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Yes, looking back on it.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Was it as good as you always hoped?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "That's the kind of music you want to get your little Chevy, get on the, you know, I don't know the Pacific Coast highway, get the shades on, ramp up the Etheridge, isn't it?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Properly in love?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, I -- myself was, I felt owed; they'll fill this up.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "So, before you felt that you'd been in love, but you haven't been able to give that person the whole you?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Terribly cheesy phrase, I know.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Have I cracked the Holy Grail of love?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on how you look at it .", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Because it's when you're the most searing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Can you write good stuff if you're really happy?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Can you?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "See, as you ask me that, this state of bliss you're talking about cannot exist without the other side, without the darker side.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "-- from the artistry of your songwriting, if I said, write, you can be in this kind of existential state of pure bliss for the next 30 years, or torment, which would produce the better music, the better songs?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "The contrast of misery, of course, is going to -- the contrast, that -- it's the desire to be out of that, into the bliss.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "What would produce the better songs?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Having been on the journey of getting towards gay and lesbian rights, equality, understanding, diversity in America, 20 years ago, started the, you know, no, I was hoping in 10 years it would all be -- we'd all feel comfortable about it.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Or are you still thinking, you know what, a lot of talk, not enough action?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "But do you feel that the them that is you and those who are, again, lesbian like you, are in a much better position now that you have a president prepared to go on television and say, \"I support\"?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Tolerance, you know, I don't even like to use the word tolerance.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Is there more tolerance?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Because it sounds like, you know, I'm doing something that you have to tolerate.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What's the right word?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Especially Kansas, because I came from the Kansas in the '60s, which was the middle of the civil rights movement.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "But you feel it's getting better, even in states like Kansas?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "And what do you think is the potential prospect of a Mitt Romney presidency?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "What -- is that linked to what you said to me, that basically you've learned to love yourself?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes, you can.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "But do you?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Wow, well, I started writing when I was 10.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "What is the longest period you've ever had, where you literally couldn't write a song, of any quality at all?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Do you get long blank periods, though?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I was being a good grownup.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "If, God forbid, you were struck again by cancer, it came back or whatever, would you take marijuana?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I want to still be creating.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What do you want to be in five years' time?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I actually haven't seen that for a long time.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "You must be proud of them, are you?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Oh that scene was easy.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Difficult to film I should think, isn't it?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Lots of virgin blood.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "To eternity vitality?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "It just seems such a tragic waste for somebody.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Why is that extraordinary?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "How's it going?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "No, I never have.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Do you dream of a fairy tale white wedding one day?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "That would be really difficult.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I am, yeah.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "You are with somebody at the moment, right?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "It's going great.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "How's that going?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Define properly.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "How many times would you say you have been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, it's better than looking and saying, she looks like (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Do you like being the object of male attention in that way?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Tell her the story.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What am I supposed to say?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "The situation.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What story?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "I'm riding her over to the thrifty, ain't I?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "He -- first of all, he's so fantastic in this movie.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Is he as nice to work with as I imagine he is?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Did she ever respond?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "No, sadly.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "You never met her?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "You know, probably not as much as I should.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Do you take much of an interesting in it?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "At this -- if -- at this very moment, I would.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Would you again?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Just because I feel like I should be more -- a little bit more informed at this moment.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I would try to simplify everything.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What's the one thing you'd change for America to make it better?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Well, I believe I have a gift of shooting archery.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "How did this happen?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "You have only been doing this for two or three years properly?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "It is instilled in me from my parents.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Where do you get that from?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I'm just smiling, because it's such an honor and a privilege to be able to do that.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "What are does it mean to be representing America in the Paralympic Games?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "That's the plan.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "You don't like coming in second, do you?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "My oldest is Carter.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "What do they make of their dad?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Not to ever come back.", "docId": "120812pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "What is the lesson you learned?", "qSentId": 737}]